{
    "id": "badd4f56434249f7b7ac8ff9d9aac255",
    "title": "If, Unless, Without",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "29e97aac28e24343bc5db2eba3bed742",
            "title": "If Or Unless",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. we don’t start now, we will be late.",
                    "description": "We use if to express condition - something which must happen first so that something else can happen.",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………….. you mend your ways, you will land in serious trouble.",
                    "description": "Unless means if not. The given sentence can also be written as: If you do not mend your ways, you will land in serious trouble. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "If",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… you don’t know the meaning of a word, you should look it up in the dictionary.",
                    "description": "We use if to express a condition. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I won’t be able to do it ……………………….. your help.",
                    "description": "Without means in the absence.",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will not be able to do it …………………………… you do not help me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. you help me, I will not be able to do it.",
                    "description": "Unless means if not.",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… you have a wonderful memory, it is important to repeat your answers.",
                    "description": "Unless means if not. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "If",
                        "Without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is not easy to get a job ………………………… you have experience.",
                    "description": "The sentence means that ‘If you do not have experience, it is not easy to get a job.’",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "if",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You cannot login ………………………….. you know the password.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Children should not play with these toys ………………………….. they are under the supervision of an adult.",
                    "description": "Unless means if not.",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "without",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………. she cannot come and see us, we will go and see her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Most wild animals do not attack people ……………………. they do not provoke them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}